sexchatindia.com 2016-09-07

# Privacy Policy, Sex Chat India

Sex Chat India (the "Site") is owned and operated by **Infinite Connections Inc./Infinite Connections LTD**

Our postal address is   
**International Offices - Infinite Connections Inc.  
Amory Building, Suite #4757, Victoria Road   
Basseterre, SAINT KITTS AND NEVIS. 

**International Offices - CHAT CONNECTIONS LTD  
1 KINGS AVENUE   
WINCHMORE HILL   
LONDON   
ENGLAND   
N21 3NA  
44 203 318 0106  
Chat Connections LTD Registrationn #:08117203  
VAT #EU196011004  
**

This website is registered with the Information Commissionaire's Office in accordance to the Data Protection Act of 1998 

**

**

We can be reached via e-mail by [clicking here](http://www.sexchatindia.com/contact)

This Privacy Policy Statement sets forth the policies and practices with respect to information or data gathered regarding subscriber and members of this Site. This is an online Site that expressly and strictly limits its membership to adults. All persons under the age of 18 are strictly prohibited from accessing or viewing the contents of this Site. 

This Site does not knowingly seek or collect any personal information or data from persons under the age of 18. 

Notice - Use of Website by the Subscriber Constitutes the Subscriber's Express Assent to the Use of Personal Information Collected by Site. 

**CAREFULLY READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT BECAUSE BY YOUR SUBSCRIPTION TO AND USE OF THIS SITE YOU WILL BE EXPRESSLY SIGNIFYING THAT YOU AGREE TO THIS POLICY STATEMENT AND THAT YOU ASSENT TO THE USE OF ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION THAT YOU SUPPLY OR THAT IS COLLECTED ABOUT YOU AS DETAILED IN THIS POLICY STATEMENT.**

**IF YOU DO NOT EXPRESSLY AGREE WITH ALL OF THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT YOU SHOULD NOT SUBSCRIBE TO OR USE THIS SITE**

**THIS WEBSITE USES Google AdWords**

This website uses the Google AdWords remarketing service and Remarketing with Google Analytics to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example using the contact form to make an enquiry. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Sex Chat India and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the Sex Chat India website. Of course, any data collected, including data from Google's Interest-based advertising or 3rd-party audience data (such as age, gender, and interests) with Google Analytics will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy. You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the [Google Ad Preferences page](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/), and if you want to you can [opt out of interest-based advertising entirely by cookie settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/) or [permanently using a browser plugin](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/). 

**_What Information About Subscribers is Collected?_**

> When any consumer signs-on as a member or subscriber of this Site that consumer will be required to provide certain personal as well as demographic information which may include, but is not necessarily limited to, the subscriber's name, address, birthday, e-mail address, gender, marital status, occupation, education, credit card number and expiration date of the credit card, username and password, and special interests or affiliations. This Site collects any and all such information and includes it in its customer database. 
> 
> If the Site features or conducts any special events, special promotions or offers, contests or polls, a subscriber of the Site may be asked to provide information in order to participate, if the subscriber voluntarily provides that information, all such information may be collected by the Site and included in its customer database. 
> 
> When a subscriber of this Site requests web pages from the Site's server or clicks on banners or other hypertext links, the Site will automatically collect some information or data about the subscriber, including the subscriber's IP address, the information that is collected may also indicate any special preferences or requests of the subscriber; all that information and data will be collected by the Site and included in its customer database. 
> 
> If a subscriber sends any personal communication or correspondence, by any means, to the Site, or any of its employees, agents or representatives, the Site may collect any information regarding that communication and include that information in its customer database. 
> 
> The Site may also automatically collect traffic and click-through data as well as information regarding the online behavior of subscribers by the use of "cookies" or other programming means - any information about subscribers collected by the Site through the use of cookies or other programming means may be included in its customer database. 
> 
> You may obtain further information about "cookies" and how they function at: <http://www.cookiecentral.com/>.

**_Use of Personal Subscriber Information._**

> The subscriber expressly agrees that the Site may use any personal information that has been provided by the subscriber or that has been collected by the Site about the subscriber for any purpose, including without limitation, technical, administration, research and development, customer administration, marketing, age verification, promotional and advertising use by the Site or third parties authorized to use the information by the Site. We do not rent, sell, or share your email address with outside parties. 
> 
> By the subscriber's use of the Site, the subscriber expressly agrees that the Site may use any of the personal information about subscribers that it has gathered or collected to provide them with offers to other sites or products that may or may not be of interest. 
> 
> Please note that personal information about a subscriber may be collected by a third-party web service provider that has an advertising banner or link on the Site. 
> 
> The Site is not responsible or liable for the use of any information that a subscriber may provide, or that is gathered by third-party web sites that have banner ads or links on the Site. This Site does not control, monitor or endorse the information gathering practices or Privacy Policies of any of those third-party web sites.
> 
> Whenever applicable, each subscriber should seek to read the Privacy Policy of any third-party web site provider that has an advertising banner, advertises or has a link on the Site.
> 
> Security of Personal Information Collected by the Site.
> 
> Consistent with the Policies set forth in this Privacy Statement, the Site has adopted and implemented reasonable and technologically feasible procedures for maintaining the security, accuracy and integrity of all personal information relating to subscribers that is collected by the Site. 
> 
> All subscribers should consider any information provided to or collected by the Site as non-confidential, and consequently the Site assumes no liability or responsibility if any information relating to any subscriber is intercepted and/or used by an unintended recipient.

**_"OPT-IN" and "OPT-OUT" Provisions._**

> There may be occasions when a subscriber will be presented with special offers either from the operators of the Site or from third-party service or content providers, which may include consent to receive e-mail solicitations, communications, newsletters, commercial advertising, or other promotional or special event materials (collectively referred to as "Offers"). 
> 
> **" OPT-IN"** \-- Some Offers may be presented to the subscriber with the option to express the subscriber's preference by either clicking or entering "accept" (alternatively "yes") or "decline" (alternatively "no"). By selecting or clicking the "accept" or "yes" the subscriber indicates that the subscriber "OPTS-IN" to that Offer and thereby agrees and assents that the subscriber's personal information and data may be disclosed to third-parties. 
> 
> **" OPT-OUT"** \-- Other Offers may be presented with a pre-selected preference or choice. If the subscriber does not deselect the pre-selected preference of choice (i.e. "OPT-OUT" of the Offer) then the Site may transfer the subscriber's personal profile information to the third-party service or content provider making the Offer. If the subscriber deselects the pre-selected preference then no personal information about the subscriber may be disclosed to any third-party service or content provider.

_**"OPT-OUT" Revocation Procedure.**_

> The Site also offers all subscribers a procedure for "Opting-Out" if the subscriber subsequently chooses to revoke any consent to receive Offers by clicking here and deselecting "I want to be informed of promotional offers".

_**Terms and Conditions of Membership.**_

> Each subscriber should carefully read each of the terms and conditions of Membership of this Site. By accepting membership to this Site you are unconditionally accepting all of those terms and conditions. Some of those terms and conditions may also affect the right of this Site to use information that it has gathered from subscribers.
> 
> In the event of any conflicts between the http://www.sexchatindia.com/pages/terms.html and this Privacy Policy Statement, the provisions of this Privacy Policy shall control.  
> 

******************
